Guide to the Abe Burrows papers, 1904-1993
The New York Public Library. Billy Rose Theatre Division.
- Series X: Personal Business Files, 1936-1990; 589632; 3 boxes
  - Sub-series 1 - Legal, 1942-1990; 589633; 1 box
    This sub-series consists of correspondence, memos, contracts, and other legal papers with various law firms engaged by Burrows. The issues are both personal and professional including papers relating to his divorce from Ruth Burrows and personal legal affairs and wills of both Abe and Carin Burrows as well as correspondence pertaining to Beresford Productions, contracts with the William Morris Agency, testimony concerning Burrows' fall into an orchestra pit, and arbitration papers concerning professional disputes over various productions. Some of Burrows' carbon copies of letters he sent, especially to Martin Gang in Box 113, Folder 1, contain lengthy accounts of his working life. The legal files concerning Burrows appearance before the House Committee on Un-American Activities are filed in Series II. Correspondence because that is where they were filed when the papers arrived at the Library.
    - Legal correspondence with Gang, Kopp & Tyre, 1942-1973; 589634; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 1)
      Correspondence is mostly on Burrows' career.
    - Legal correspondence with Reinheimer & Cohen, 1951-1954; 589635; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 2)
      Correspondence is on personal legal matters.
    - Legal correspondence with Robert Morris, 1959-1977; 589636; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 3)
      Correspondence is on personal and professional matters,
    - Robert Morris file on financial problems with Evelyn Greene, 1971-1975; 589637; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and memos with William Morris Agency, 1960-1977; 589638; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Contracts: Burrows and William Morris Agency, 1960-1969; 589639; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, testimony and other legal papers on Burrows vs. The Bartlett Co., 1973-1976; 589640; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 7)
      Material concerns the case stemming from Burrows' fall into an orchestra pit, 1973 Feb 6.
    - Legal correspondence between Abe and Carin Burrows and Stanford Schewel, 1982-1985; 589641; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 8)
      Includes Abe Burrows' death certificate.
    - Legal correspondence between Carin Burrows and Stanford Schewel, 1986-1990; 589642; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and legal papers on Abe Burrows divorce from his first wife, Ruth, 1948-1983; 589643; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Wills and related papers for Abe Burrows, 1960-1982; 589644; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Wills for Carin Burrows and papers related to her parents' wills and estates, 1960-1982; 589645; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Sub-series 2 - Financial, 1948-1984; 589646; 1 box
    This sub-series contains Burrows' correspondence with his accountant concerning his financial affairs and papers relating to various real estate transactions and non-theatrical business deals.
    - Correspondence with accountant, Julius Lefkowitz, 1948-1960; 589647; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with accountant, Julius Lefkowitz, 1961-1974; 589648; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with accountant, Julius Lefkowitz, 1975-1984; 589649; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence on real estate investments, 1949-1964; 589650; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, reports and minutes on proposal to purchase real estate in California, 1964-1965; 589651; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Papers on a property transaction, Provincetown, Massachusetts, 1971; 589652; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, contracts, minutes and financial reports pertaining to River Enterprises, 1950-1954; 589653; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, contracts and reports on answering services investment, 1960-1963; 589654; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, contracts and reports on answering services investment, 1966-1971; 589655; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and contracts pertaining to Lopen Properties limited partnership, 1967; 589656; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, memos, contracts and financial statements pertaining to Princess Company limited partnership, 1968-1981; 589657; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Contract on Pip's Restaurant limited partnership, 1969; 589658; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Sub-series 3 - Miscellaneous personal: medical, insurance, taxes and homes, 1936-1985; 589659; 1 box
    This sub-series contains correspondence and claims with insurance companies, medical reports and medicare claims from the end of his life, tax data, bank loans, and correspondence and leases for his homes in New York City and Provincetown, Massachusetts including correspondence on furnishing his apartment at the Beresford.
    - Insurance claims data, 1952-1961; 589660; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Insurance loans, 1952-1958; 589661; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and related papers with insurers, Bloomgarden & Liesner, 1955-1961; 589662; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and related papers with insurers, Bloomgarden & Liesner, and other companies, 1960-1976; 589663; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and medical reports, 1950-1983; 589664; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Medicare claims, 1980-1985; 589665; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Tax forms and correspondence, 1942-1955 & 1974; 589666; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Income computation, 1952; 589667; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Notes payable, 1954-1955 and n.d; 589668; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Bank loans, 1954-1961; 589669; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Leases and correspondence pertaining to Burrows' apartment at the Beresford, 1949-1959; 589670; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and other papers relating to homes in New York City and Provincetown, Massachusetts, 1936-1972; 589671; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and bills for decorating and furnishing apartment at the Beresford, 1953-1954; 589672; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 16)
- Series XI: Clippings, 1943-1985 and n.d; 589673; 1 box and 2 volumes
  Consists of photocopied clippings about Burrows as well as some press releases and two scrapbooks of clippings that he kept and that have not been photocopied.
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1943-1946; 589674; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1947; 589675; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Press releases about Burrows, 1948-1950; 589676; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1948 Jan-Apr; 589677; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1948 May-July; 589678; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1948 Aug; 589679; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1948 Sept-Oct; 589680; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1948 Nov-Dec; 589681; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1949; 589682; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1950; 589683; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1951; 589684; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1952-1959; 589685; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1960s; 589686; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1970s; 589687; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Clippings about Burrows, 1980s; 589688; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 15)
    Includes Honest Abe and obituaries.
  - Clippings and press releases about Burrows, 589689; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Letters and other papers on publicity for Burrows, 1947-1962; 589690; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Clipping on Carin Burrows, ca. 1940; 589691; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Clippings mainly about others, 1950-1977; 589692; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 19)
    Some are about weddings or funerals where Burrows spoke.
  - Scrapbook of clippings, "A,", 1943-1950; 589693; 1 volume (Volume 117, Folder 1)
    On verso of cover, "Abe Burrows, Hollywood, Calif.
  - Scrapbook of clippings, "B,", 1946 Jan-1947 Dec; 589694; 1 volume (Volume 118, Folder 1)
- Series XII: Photographs and Other Visual Materials, 1914-1993; 589695; 3 boxes
  Photographs of Burrows are mainly formal portraits or photos of Burrows with colleagues on sets for television talk shows, at parties and formal dinners, etc. Includes photos of Burrows with Lauren Bacall, Milton Berle, Carol Channing, Marlene Dietrich, Moss Hart, President Lyndon Johnson, Steve Lawrence, Frank Loesser, Ethel Merman, Marilyn Monroe, Dinah Shore, Gloria Swanson Gore Vidal, Mike Wallace and many others. There is also a folder of the photographs used in his autobiography, Honest Abe which includes childhood and family portraits as well as duplicates of photos of Abe with some of the very well known people with whom he worked. The series also includes a few sketches and caricatures of Burrows. All visual materials in this series are small enough to fit in standard-sized hollinger boxes.
  Formal portraits of Burrows are followed by photographs of him at work arranged chronologically and then photos with others, mostly undated, arranged alphabetically by the name of the other, followed by family snapshots and photos with unknowns. At the end of the series is artwork, primarily drawings of Burrows by others.
  - Portraits of Abe Burrows by Arnold Newman, n.d.; 589696; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 1)
    Consists of master prints, mounted.
  - Portraits of Abe Burrows by Arnold Newman, n.d.; 589697; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 2)
    Contains prints and contact sheets.
  - Portraits of Abe Burrows by Otto Storch, n.d.; 589698; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Portraits of Abe Burrows by various photographers, 1951-1974 and n.d; 589699; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Photographers' names are stamped on back of prints.
  - Portraits of Abe Burrows, uncredited, 1962 and n.d; 589700; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Abe Burrows on the nightclub circuit, n.d.; 589701; 1 folder (3 photos) (Box 119, Folder 6)
    Includes House of Harris in San Francisco and the Mayfair Room in Chicago. One photograph is signed by George Fox.
  - Abe Burrows on the radio, 1940s-1950s; 589702; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Duffy's Tavern (radio program), Early 1940s; 589703; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 119, Folder 8)
    With Ed Gardner.
  - Abe Burrows with the Milton DeLugg quartet, 1948-1950; 589704; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 9)
    On radio, television and on the road.
  - Abe Burrows with Guys and Dolls cast members and producers, 589705; 1 folder (3 photos) (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Abe Burrows and others on the television program This Is Show Business, 589706; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 11)
    Includes Gloria Swanson, Gypsy Rose Lee, Bert Lahr and George S. Kaufman.
  - Abe Burrows and others promoting National Fur Care Week on the television program, This Is Show Business, 589707; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Abe Burrows and others on the television showWe Take Your Word, 1950-1951.; 589708; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 13)
    Includes Faye Emerson, Jeannette MacDonald and Eva LeGallienne.
  - Abe Burrows on television, 1950s-1970s; 589709; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 14)
    Includes Carol Channing, Art Carney, Ossie Davis and Ruby Dee.
  - Prints and a few negatives of Abe Burrows on television with Mike Wallace, 1960s; 589710; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 15)
    Includes Eva Gabor, Eartha Kitt, Tony Bennett and others.
  - Abe Burrows at Paramount Pictures, 1955; 589711; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Snapshots from summer in Hollywood, 1955; 589712; 1 folder (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Party at Nunnally Johnson's, 1946; 589713; 1 folder (one photo) (Box 120, Folder 1)
    Includes Abe Burrows, Robert Benchley, Danny Kaye, Marc Connelly and the back of Groucho Marx's head.
  - National Father's Day Committee, Father of the Year ceremony, 1951; 589714; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Dramatists Guild officers, late 1950s; 589715; 1 folder (one photo) (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Abe Burrows at the Tony Awards, 1962; 589716; 1 folder (one photo) (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Judy Holliday Memorial, 1966; 589717; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 5)
    Includes Leonard Bernstein, Henry Fonda, Betty Comden, Adolph Green, Robert Kennedy and Abe Burrows.
  - At Billy Rose's New Year's Eve party at the Ziegfeld Theatre, 1949; 589718; 1 folder (one photo) (Box 120, Folder 6)
    Includes Frank and Lynn Loesser, Carol Channing and Abe and Carin Burrows.
  - William Morris 75th anniversary party, n.d.; 589719; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Abe Burrows' book party, 1980?; 589720; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 8)
    Includes Ethel Merman and Lou Jacoby.
  - Abe Burrows at black tie events with unidentified others, n.d.; 589721; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Bridge game with Sir Cedric Hardwicke, Ilke Chase, Julie Wilson and Abe Burrows, 589722; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Fundraising for the Federation of Jewish Philanthropies, 589723; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Edward Albee, James Burrows, Abe Burrows and Uta Hagen, 1965; 589724; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Morcy Amsterdam, Lee Tracy and Abe Burrows, 589725; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Julie Andrews and Abe Burrows, 589726; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Lauren Bacall and Abe Burrows, 1960s; 589727; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 15)
    Includes Jason Robarts, John Mills and Barry Nelson.
  - Jack Benny and Abe Burrows, late 1940s; 589728; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Mimi Benzell and Abe Burrows, 589729; 1 folder (3 photos) (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Milton Berle and Abe Burrows, 589730; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Janet Blair, Abe Burrows and others, 589731; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Sammy Cahn and Abe Burrows, 589732; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Carol Channing and Abe Burrows, 1970; 589733; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 21)
    Signed by Channing.
  - Joan Collins, Anthony Newley, Shelley Winter, Orson Bean and Abe Burrows, 589734; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Noel Coward, Abe and Carin Burrows and others, 589735; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Bing Crosby and Abe Burrows, mid 1950s; 589736; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Marlene Dietrich with Abe Burrows and with Ed Gardner, 589737; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Ralph Edwards, Steve Lawrence, John Williams, Abe Burrows and unidentified, 589738; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Clifton Fadiman, Harry Kurnitz, Abe Burrows and others, 589739; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - John Gielgud, Tallulah Bankhead and Abe Burrows, early 1950s; 589740; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - John Glenn, Rudy Vallee, Robert Morse and Abe Burrows, 1962; 589741; 1 folder (3 photos) (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Julie Harris and Abe Burrows, 589742; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Moss Hart and Abe Burrows, 1950s; 589743; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Judy Holliday, Paul Douglas, Abe Burrows and his children, 1955; 589744; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Georgie Jessel, Abe Burrows and others, 589745; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Lyndon Johnson, Duke Ellington, Abe Burrows and others, 589746; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Ed Koch, Tammy Grimes, David Merrick, Jerry Orbach, Abe Burrows and others, 589747; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 35)
    Signed by Ed Koch.
  - Governor Lane of Maryland, Abe Burrows and members of the Advertising Club of Baltimore, 589748; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - Steve Lawrence and Abe Burrows, 589749; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - Peggy Lee and Abe Burrows, 589750; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - Frank Loesser and Abe Burrows, 1947 and n.d; 589751; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 39)
    Includes one photo from the Abe Burrows Show(radio).
  - Mary Martin, Abe Burrows and others, 589752; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 40)
  - Lee Marvin and Abe Burrows, 1960s; 589753; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 41)
  - Ethel Merman and Abe Burrows, early 1950s; 589754; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 42)
  - Marilyn Monroe, Tex McCrary and Abe Burrows, 589755; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 43)
  - Jane Pickens, Abe Burrows and others, 589756; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 44)
  - Tom Poston, Elaine May, Mike Nichols, Abe Burrows and unidentified, 589757; 1 folder (3 photos) (Box 120, Folder 45)
  - Harold Rome and Abe Burrows, ca. mid 1950s; 589758; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 46)
  - Billy Rose, Eleanor Holm, Jack O'Brien, Abe Burrows, and others, 1950s; 589759; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 47)
  - Dinah Shore and Abe Burrows, 1947; 589760; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 48)
  - Lee Strassberg and Abe Burrows, 589761; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 49)
  - Gloria Swanson and Abe Burrows, 1950s; 589762; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 50)
  - Gore Vidal and Abe Burrows, 589763; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 120, Folder 51)
  - John Woodruff, Leo Gaffney, Peggy Doyle, Mary Sullivan, Abe Burrows and others, 589764; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 120, Folder 52)
  - Photographs and transparencies for Honest Abe, 589765; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 53)
  - Abe and Carin Burrows and others dining out, 1960 and n.d; 589766; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Snapshots: family and friends, ca. 1914-1963 and n.d; 589767; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Abe Burrows with unidentified others, n.d.; 589768; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of others, some signed to Burrows, n.d.; 589769; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 4)
    Includes Jimmy Durante, Harry Kurnitz, Jack Dempsey, Barbara Rush, Moss Hart, David Merrick, Alice Faye and John Payne, among others.
  - Transparencies: NYU lobby display on Abe Burrows' career, 1993; 589770; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Negatives: mostly travel snapshots, 1950s-1960s; 589771; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Photographic print and negative of Paul Alter's sketch of Abe Burrows, 1960; 589772; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Cartoon drawings by Doug Anderson of Abe Burrows, 1952 Mar; 589773; 1 folder (1 item) (Box 121, Folder 8)
    For New York Times Magazine.
  - Sketches by Abner Dean, n.d.; 589774; 1 folder (33 sketches) (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of caricatures by Wachsteter, n.d.; 589775; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 10)
    Drawings are of Abe Burrows, Clifton Fadiman and George Kaufman.
  - Slides of cartoon caricatures of Burrows by various artists, n.d.; 589776; 1 folder (15 images on 45 slides) (Box 121, Folder 11)
- Series XIII: Oversized Visual, 1942-1991; 589777; 5 boxes and 3 map case size folders
  This series contains photographs, artwork, certificates, an advertising mock-up for Abe Burrows Songbook and a souvenir program that were too large to fit in standard-sized hollinger boxes as well as posters for productions with which Burrows was associated. The artwork consists of caricatures and cartoons and a set design for Holly Golightly.
  Photographs (formal portraits arranged alpabetically by photographer, followed by photos of Burrows with others arranged chronologically); artwork; certificates; ad layout; souvenir program (3 boxes: 15 in. x 19 in. or less); followed by: photographs; artwork; certificates; theater posters (alphabetical by title) (2 boxes: 21 in. x 25 in. or less); followed by three items in map drawer.
  - Photographic portrait, signed, by Cecil Beaton of Abe Burrows, n.d.; 589778; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Photographic portraits by Philippe Halsman of Abe Burrows, n.d.; 589779; 1 folder (3 photos) (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Photographic portrait, signed, by Lotti Jacobi of Abe Burrows, n.d.; 589780; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Photographic portraits of Abe Burrows, photographers unknown, n.d.; 589781; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Ed Gardner, Abe Burrows and others, 1942 Nov 16 and n.d; 589782; 1 folder (2 photos) (Box 123, Folder 1)
    One photo is signed by the writers of Duffy's Tavern; the other includes Burrows' young son, Jimmy.
  - Party at Nunnally Johnson's, 1946; 589783; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 123, Folder 2)
    Includes Abe Burrows at the piano with Nunnally Johnson, Danny Kaye, Robert Benchley, Marc Connelly, Norman Corwin, Ira Gershwin and Groucho Marx.
  - Milton Berle and Abe Burrows, early 1950s; 589784; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Three Wishes for Jamie cast members, Ann Jeffreys and John Raitt, with Abe and Carin Burrows, 1952; 589785; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Say, Darling cast members, Vivian Blaine, J. Desmond, David Wayne and others with Abe Burrows, 1958; 589786; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Frank Loesser and Abe Burrows, 1962 May; 589787; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 123, Folder 6)
    Congratulating each other on winning the Pulitzer Prize for How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying.
  - "Theatrical summit session,", 1962 May; 589788; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 123, Folder 7)
    "Leading lights of Broadway theater" meet with White House consultant on the Arts, August Heckscher.
  - Joan Davis, (signed to Abe Burrows), ca. late 1940s; 589789; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Caricature by Abner Dean of Abe Burrows, n.d.; 589790; 1 folder (1 drawing) (Box 124, Folder 1)
    In pencil and signed.
  - Photoprint of Al Hirschfeld's caricature of How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, 1962; 589791; 1 folder (1 drawing) (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Set design by Oliver Smith for Holly Golightly, 1965; 589792; 1 folder (1 drawing) (Box 124, Folder 3)
    In watercolor.
  - Marriage certificate, 1950 Oct 2; 589793; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 4)
    For Abe Burrows and Elsie Marie Kinzel (given name of Carin Burrows)
  - Awards and certificates, 1949-1951; 589794; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 5)
    Includes NY Drama Critics Circle Award for Guys and Dolls.
  - Advertising mock-up for Abe Burrows Songbook, n.d.; 589795; 1 folder (1 item) (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Souvenir program for 42nd Street, 1980?; 589796; 1 folder (1 item) (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Photographic portrait signed by Irving Penn of Abe Burrows, 1951; 589797; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Photographic portrait of Burrows sneezing, n.d.; 589798; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Tony Awards dinner, 1951 Mar 25; 589799; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Abe Burrows, Cy Feuer and Frank Loesser at work on How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, 1961; 589800; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - President Kennedy at How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, at the 46th Street Theatre, 1962 Jan 19; 589801; 1 folder (1 photo) (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Cartoon by Carl Rose, n.d.; 589802; 1 folder (1 drawing in 2 pieces) (Box 125, Folder 6)
    Ink and wash, signed.
  - Certificate naming the Abe Burrows Theatre at New York University, 1991 Mar 14; 589803; 1 folder (1 item) (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Posters for Cactus Flower, 1965; 589804; 1 folder (2 posters) (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Poster for Can-Can, 1953; 589805; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Poster for First Impressions, 1959; 589806; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Posters for Forty Carats, 1968 and later; 589807; 1 folder (2 posters) (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Poster for Four on a Garden, 1971; 589808; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Poster for Golden Fleecing, 1959; 589809; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Poster for Good News, 1974; 589810; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Poster for Guys and Dolls, 1992; 589811; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 8)